You better believe.
Rise of the Guardians is a animation, family,
fantasy film directed by Peter Ramsey.
When an evil spirit known as Pitch lays down the gauntlet to take over the world, the immortal Guardians must join
forces for the first time to protect the hopes, beliefs and imagination of children all over the world.
Jack Frost (voice), played by Chris Pine.
North (voice), played by Alec Baldwin.
Pitch (voice), played by Jude Law.
Tooth (voice), played by Isla Fisher.
Bunny (voice), played by Hugh Jackman.
Jamie Bennett (voice), played by Dakota Goyo.
Rise of the Guardians is a 2012 American animated science fantasy action-adventure film directed by Peter Ramsey and written by David
Lindsay-Abaire, based on the book series The Guardians of Childhood and the short film The Man in the Moon by William Joyce.
Produced by DreamWorks Animation, the film stars the voices of Chris
Pine, Alec Baldwin, Jude Law, Isla Fisher, and Hugh Jackman.
The film tells a story about Guardians Santa Claus, the Tooth Fairy, the Easter Bunny, and the Sandman, who
enlist Jack Frost to stop Pitch Black from engulfing the world in darkness in a fight of dreams.
Rise of the Guardians premiered at the Mill Valley Film Festival on October 10, 2012, and was theatrically released in
the United States by Paramount Pictures on November 21, and received positive reviews from critics.
Despite grossing $306.9 million worldwide against a budget of $145 million, it was a box-office failure
and lost the studio an estimated $87 million due to marketing and distribution costs.
It was nominated for the Golden Globe Award for Best Animated Feature
Film and the Annie Award for Best Animated Feature.
The film explores themes of new york city,
friendship, amnesia, santa claus, cartoon.